# LAUREL THORBURN, AuD, CCC-A

Area: Aurora, CO 80016 | Phone: 303-736-9393 | Email: codinglaurel@gmail.com

GitHub: https://github.com/laurelthorburn

#### WEB DEVELOPER

Creative and proficient object-oriented web developer with extensive history of working in client facing, team-oriented roles. Fast learner who's reliable, enthusiastic, and methodical. Experience with MERN stack, CSS, semantic and accessible HTML, JavaScript, jQuery, React, NoSQL, MySql, Express, and Node.js.

## **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

- Accessibility
- Bootstrap/Bulma
- CSS
- Express
- Git

- GraphQL
- Heroku
- HTML
- JavaScript/jQuery
- Jest

- MySQL/NoSQL
- NextJS
- Node
- ReactJS
- TypeScript

## **PROJECTS**

## DONUT-FORGET | https://github.com/laurelthorburn/DONUT-FORGET-TO-REVIEW

Full stack application utilizing Node.js, Sequelize, MySql, Handlebars, and Cloudinary. Site allows users to create posts with images, leave comments, and login/logout of their session to keep their data secure by using local storage and cookies.

"React Portfolio" | https://laurelthorburn.github.io/Laurel-Thorburn-Portfolio/

Created a responsive, mobile first, single page application portfolio using React.js, EmailJS, and Node. User is able to render an about page, contact page, resume, and projects of Laurel Thorburn. Weather Dashboard | https://github.com/laurelthorburn/Weather-Dashboard

Created a user-friendly weather dashboard that uses a third-party API, openweathermap.org, to fetch weather data and store results in local storage. Results are dynamically created using JavaScript and jQuery and are displayed in cards created by a CSS library, Bootstrap.

### **EXPERIENCE**

# **Kaiser Permanente: Lead Clinical Audiologist**

11/2019 - present

Working with pediatric and adult patients providing diagnostic and rehabilitation services, such as audiological evaluations, hearing aid consultations, and fittings.

Aurora/Cherry Creek Public Schools: Educational Audiologist

07/2017 - 10/2019

Worked with students, ages 0 to 21 years of age, and families of diverse cultures, backgrounds, languages, and disorders providing audiological evaluations and services.

## **EDUCATION**

University Denver (DU), Denver, CO

08/2021 - present

Full Stack Developer Certificate

University of Colorado (CU), Boulder, CO

08/2013 - 05/2017

Doctorate of Audiology (AuD)